easyfreeware.com 2011-05-25

# Easy Freeware | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how easyfreeware.com uses and protects any information that you give while using this website. 

#### Information collection rules

Please be aware that we may collect certain technical information to ensure that our service is functioning properly. Such technical information includes: the IP address from which our website was accessed, browser type, your operating system and its version, screen resolution. We may also collect the data informing us on how you reached our website, what technologies were used to access it and what pages interest our visitors the most. 

We do not collect personally identifiable information about our visitors without their consent. However if a visitor has submitted his/her private data such as names, postal addresses, e-mail addresses voluntarily this information will be kept secure and protected, will not be shared with any other organization, nor will it be sold or bartered unless otherwise stated. 

#### Data collected will be used for:

\- Providing our visitors with the high-quality and efficient information and service 

\- Notifying consumers about updates to our Web site 

\- Promoting our archive of free software resources 

\- Bringing the website in accordance with visitors' interests, search engine optimization requirements and marketing purposes 

#### Cookies

We may use an outside ad serving company to display banner advertisements on our site. As part of their service, they will generally store a separate cookie on your computer to record information including which advertisement visitors followed to reach the advertiser's website, and the date when they visited. Depending on the advertiser's practices cookies will be deleted after different lengths of time. 

Our site is also supported by Google Adsense service. The ads provided are relevant to the information published on the website and / or page they are on (i.e. the information is retrieved from the website contents not the visitors themselves). Google Adsense uses cookies to publish ads on our site. Google's use of DART cookies makes it possible to serve ads to the users based on their visit to the current site and to other sites on the Internet. A user may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

#### Published information contents

The software catalog of easyfreeware.com offers the unique opportunity to an interested person or an organization to publish the information about his/her software products and to make it available to a huge audience of visitors. Please note that easyfreeware.com does not bear responsibility for the contents of the information made available in our catalog. In case of any claims or complaints to the contents of the information or to the quality of the software product offered please contact the corresponding publisher, not the staff of easyfreeware.com. 

#### Commitment to data security

Our website will usually provide you with the links through which you may access other sites. You should take into account that as soon as you leave easyfreeware.com we are no longer responsible for the protection of your private information. Therefore we do encourage you to read privacy policy, data collection, use and disclosure practices of the web site you are on in order to determine how your personal information is treated. 

#### Contact us

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using our e-mail:  
[editor@easyfreeware.com](mailto:editor@easyfreeware.com).
